(Raj:)And you think
that's going to help?
Yes.
(Howard:)Well, I don't think
that's gonna help at all.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, it will.
(Sheldon:)See, by keeping my mind engaged,
I'll become more focused.
(Leonard:)Howard's right--
that'll never work.
(Sheldon:)Stop fighting me on the premise.
(Sheldon:)It's scientifically valid.
(Sheldon:)I'm going to advance
propositions,
(Sheldon:)I just want you to challenge me.
(Howard:)I don't think that's
what you want at all.
(Sheldon:)Why, of course it's what I want.
(Sheldon:)Why would I say it's what I want
if it's not what I want?
(Leonard:)Because it is what you want,
and it's not what you said.
(Sheldon:)I ask you for one simple thing,
and you can't even do it.
(Howard:)Yes, we can.
Yeah, well, then do it.
(Howard:)Nah.
(Sheldon:)You guys are the worst.
(Sheldon:)Thank you,
I think that was helpful.
(Penny:)So, whichever rep has
the best sales for the quarter
(Penny:)gets a trip for two to Hawaii.
(Amy:)That would be so romantic
for you and Leonard.
(Penny:)Yeah, clearly you haven't
seen him on the beach